I'm gonna turn around.
It's cute.
It's cute, but...
Which one is Mt Fuji?
This one, of all places.
Are you good at taking pictures?
Not good.
You take good selfies, Airi.
I suck at selfies.
You're so cute!
It's getting hot.
Good night.
I lifted Mt.
What should I do with it?
Let's make a stone Mt Fuji like this.
Like this... can you put a Mt Fuji inside?
Is it in there?
Yes, it's in there.
It looks good, doesn't it?
It looks great.
I can see it.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Oh, it looks good.
That's good.
The end.
The members are looking restless as Mr. Takahiro will be here tomorrow night before the presentation.
I still can't keep up with their speed, so I'll do my best to dance properly.
Ima-chan only slept for an hour and a half.
But it's too bad, because if I tell you that, your expectations will be high.
I've been working really hard, practicing dance all morning even after waking up.
Good morning.
Did you all sleep well yesterday?
Practicing is important, but it's also important to sleep and eat.
Let's work hard for tomorrow's presentation!
Mr. Takahiro has already started his take.
Good morning.
I hear you've been working very hard.
I hear it's hard work every day.
Did any of you come to see the Asuno concert at Sakurazaka?
Everyone is aiming to exceed that concert by 100%.
As you may have heard several times, you are now part of the Sakurazaka group.
But whether or not you can go on stage is still up in the air.
Because you still need to be good enough to perform in that concert.
So, it must have been a hard time for you. I hope you can become one of them as soon as possible.
Let's get on with the rest of the day.
Thank you very much.
Takahiro Sensei stared at him during the lesson without saying a word.
Kojima-san, who's always worrying about others, got sick and had to take some time off from practice.
You're so expressive, Matomo-chan!
Yes, her eyes are especially wonderful!
You were so easy to follow.
Yes, amazing, amazing!
I still haven't mastered some of the steps.
I haven't caught up with some of the steps yet.
But I can see that you're getting comfortable enough to make facial expressions.
I could see that you are getting more comfortable with it.
As we repeat the same lesson day after day
Sometimes I wonder if I'm really moving forward.
Nakajima-chan sang so well!
Maybe the best among the three of us.
Compared to the first day, her movements are much bigger.
You've become a totally different group!
Compared to yesterday, you've grown up so much!
Thank you so much for your hard work.
Good job, good job, good job.
You did a great job, you had the face of a person who is performing well, so it was great!
At first Murayama was not so confident, but she danced with confidence, and then she cried because she was so frustrated that she couldn't keep her stamina until the end of the lesson.
Takahiro-sensei, who had been watching the lesson for a long time, opened his mouth.
Takahiro, who had been watching the lesson, opened his mouth
You are doing very well. I think she has learned the choreography and is doing well.
The other good thing is that everyone's eyes were alive. When you run side by side, it tends to be a short-distance race.
But what is more important is to look at the middle and long distances. Because from here on out
There are many more things to come. When you really get on stage, where will you be at that moment? So it is better not to go wow and run out of breath.
It is important to have a yardstick. It is important to have a short yardstick and a long yardstick.
Always remember that you have two yardsticks. It is very important to know how far this small memory has grown compared to today or yesterday.
It is still too early to stand on stage as Sakurazaka46. But it is very important to know that your memory is increasing to get closer to the stage as Sakurazaka46.
All right, I will see you tomorrow. Thank you very much.
This was the last day of voice training.
Except for those who sing, you should seriously support those who are singing.
That's the subject of the last lesson.
When you experience singing with someone cheering you on...
I can enjoy it, I can relax a little, because everyone was there.
I feel like I was able to see the quality of expression that transcended the voice being inverted or not.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
This is the last lesson today and the last lesson throughout the camp.
I want to thank all of you for your hard work. Give yourself a little pat on the back. You did your best, you did your best.
I think you did it because you had a strong will to finish the dance.
I am sure that one day you will be able to lead Sakurazaka.
Have fun tomorrow.
I'm looking forward to seeing the future of the 3rd term students.
Yes, I am looking forward to the future of the 3rd term students.
Well then, thank you very much. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Let's go!
A-A-O!
Let's go!Let's go for it!
To the 3rd term students who finished all the lessons
The famous "SAKAMICHI", "ZEKEN" with their names on it, was handed out.
A-A-O!
Strangely enough, wearing this number gives me a boost of energy, doesn't it?
Finally, the last day of the training camp, I'm fired up, all I need to do now is to show the results of my practice.
I want to cheer someone up I want to break out of my shell I want to have confidence in myself
BGM
Seino, thank you very much for your time!
Thank you for watching.
I'm the only one who says things I'm the only one who says things
I'm the only one who says things I'm the only one who says things I'm the only one who says things I'm the only one who says things
I'm sure I can't do it anymore, but that's okay
I've been looking for someone to hold me, someone to tell me
Don't rush me to change my mind
I feel that my feelings are growing on my face, and I feel that I have room to grow.
It was easy to understand that I felt the song and the lyrics and expressed them in my mind, and I am glad that my heart was in it.
Thank you very much.
In the second half, I had more time to look forward.
Usually, when I feel more and more pressure, I tend to look down more and more in the second half, saying that I am not good enough.
On the other hand, Odagura, who had tended to look down, started to spend more and more time looking forward, saying, "I'm going to do this.
One good part of the performance was when he turned his back for a moment.
I liked the fact that even when they turned their backs for a moment, they did not lose their attention and showed it properly.
Hey!
He was always looking at his chest.
That's no way to wake up.
I'm so blissed out by everything.
I'm here today, too.
It's a shame.
Then there was justice.
How could you be so malicious?
I'm the only one who'll take my hand.
I'll take your hand... if you'll just let me take your hand.
I'll stay with you
But I can be different now
It's not the future
If you notice that I'm still here...
I'll give you a chance to say it over again
Do you understand?
You'll be sweating all over the place.
Now, will you shed a tear?
I don't know where the standard is.
Pea, is this the same pea that couldn't remember how to dance yesterday?
Yes.
Today's Endo is supposed to be the Endo who has learned all the moves.
Thank you very much.
Of course, I'm not ready to go live.
By a long measure, I mean.
But I saw Endo's yardstick yesterday.
Endo has grown up a lot.
Thank you very much.
And with the bouncing, it's very detailed.
There's the part where you make it with your hands.
He's able to do that much?
That was a surprise.
I thought Taniguchi was leading this group this time.
I think his eyes are the strongest of all the people I've seen so far today.
There's the other side inside Taniguchi.
Taniguchi probably knows how to control himself.
But Taniguchi's body can move so much more.
Please spend more time on opening up now.
Nakajima often wonders, "What kind of music is this?
Nakajima is the type of person who can bring out the charm of a piece by thinking carefully about what kind of music it is.
It's not so much technique.
Nakajima has a great empathy for music.
Nakajima is the type of person who can feel the music and feel the pain in his heart.
I think he is the type of person who can feel the pain and the joy of music.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm going to go to the trouble of spitting it out, even if it's just a dream.
If you say it's the same now, it's not impossible.
I'm going to go out of my way to say it out, no matter who you say it is.
I won't go to the trouble of staying away from them, meeting them, and doing something about it.
Someday I'll have to look at it. It's not enough.
Wow, please, I want to run with that standard.
Thank you very much.
Great!
I can imagine Murayama in the group now.
The performance of this van...
It's like they're struggling to make it.
You can see that they are just going for it.
His eyes are looking forward and his feelings
He probably grew up a lot in this group.
Ishimori's accent was good, too.
The part where he said "Gan" was very bold.
He has such a gentle body.
I wondered where he got the power to be so bold.
So, the power to jump is your weapon.
Let's first develop your ability to jump in.
What do you mean by "bang"?
It's one of the songs in Sakurazaka that you have to train hard for.
I heard some people worried about it at the beginning.
I was telling them that it's impossible to do a bang.
But I told them that if they could do it, they might be able to do it, and I said, "Let's believe in them.
We decided to do the van.
We were just talking about how many of us would be able to stay for the last day, and who would be able to make it.
It was just a matter of time.
But at the end of the day, it turned out that
I can't imagine that we were able to get to the point where everyone
I am very happy that we were able to bring it to the point where everyone was able to perform to the very end.The first thing I can say is that it was more than I expected.
To sum up, when it comes to the Sakurazaka stage
Let's say the level at which you can appear on the Sakurazaka stage is 100.
I'd say everyone now is between 70 and 50.
50 is still a pendulum to learn from.
But it's not 30, it's not 20, it's over 50, and that's a big deal.
Because when we started, we were at zero.
The more you do it, the more it grows.
We will continue to push you to the very edge so that what you have done will take shape when you get on stage.
We look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Please be aware that today is not the end, but the beginning.
May I?
May I? May I?
Yes, sir.
Okay, that's enough.
Okay, that's it for today. That's it for my test.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
We'd like you to complete the bun.
The next task will be to make sure that you dance the van off-size with co-mation.
Depending on the history with it, we will decide whether or not to make a music video for the third ward students.
If we only aim higher and higher, it may end up being a boring piece of work.